imodules.com 2016-09-04

# iModules Software - Privacy & Website Security Policy

### Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy for Client Constituents

iModules Software has created this privacy policy statement in order to demonstrate its firm commitment to privacy and to describe the information-gathering and dissemination practices for the website.

This website may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process involving the website.

**Cookies**  
This website uses cookies to recognize you and allow you to automatically log in without re-entering your user name and password each time you visit our site. The cookies are encrypted and do not save any personally identifiable information (see the Personally Identifiable Information section below) about you, such as your user name, password, or email address. If cookies are disabled in your browser, you can still use the site but you will be required to enter your password each time you visit.

**Personally Identifiable Information**  
This site's registration form requires you to provide your full name, address, email address, password, gender, city, state, country, and zip code. You may also choose to provide optional details, such as maiden name, nickname, birthday, occupation, company, spouse's name, photos, or personal comments. You may update any of this information at any time by accessing your profile by clicking the "edit account information" link, or equivalent, in the navigation menu. You may opt out of receiving email communications from this community (see the "Email Subscription/Opt-Out" section below). All date of birth data values are stored encrypted. Please note we do not allow clients to store any Personally Identifiable Information relating to Social Security Numbers, Driver License Numbers, or any other government issued identification. 

**Personal Profile Information and Profile Page**  
Your Personal Profile features information you may wish to share with other site members on your Profile Page. Only people who are members of this site can view other members' Profile Pages. The only information automatically displayed on your Profile Page is your First Name, Last Name, and selected additional information. Additional information fields from your Personal Profile information — including comments and other personal information you choose to share, along with any photos — will appear only if you have opted to provide those items and have also selected to have those fields in your Profile Page View.

**Credit Card Transactions**  
Some features of this site enable credit card transactions. These features are completely voluntary to members. They include the purchasing of event registrations, merchandise purchases, online donations, membership purchases, or the payment of other types of fees through the site. The operators of this site would like to assure you that measures have been taken to make such transactions secure for its members. This site uses industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) servers on our transaction pages. It encrypts all of your personal information including name, address, and credit card number to prevent unauthorized access as the information travels over the Internet. iModules takes the responsibility of your cardholder data seriously and maintains compliance with Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards (PCI DSS) by meeting all security requirements to help ensure commerce-based transaction data is protected. 

**Fraudulent Behavior**  
This is a community site that is based primarily on member input. This site cannot guarantee the accuracy of information presented. However, anyone demonstrated to have engaged in fraudulent behavior may be subject to (but not limited to) loss of privileges as a member as well as face prosecution to the fullest extent of the law.

**Safe Harbor**  
iModules Software complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. iModules Software has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program and to view iModules' certification, please visit [www.export.gov/safeharbor/](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/).

**Email Subscription Opt-Out**  
The site provides you with the opportunity to choose to receive email communications about this site and the groups you are registered with, as well as emails from other members. In all email communications you receive from this community — except confirmation emails for event registrations, purchases, donations, or other payments — you will be provided an unsubscribe option to opt out of the specific email communication type. You can also modify the email types you receive at any time by going to your account profile and changing your opt-in status.

**Photo, Blog, and other Personal Content Policy**  
This site retains the right to remove or reject any content that it deems obscene or objectionable, or has been reported as such by other members. In addition, the client licensors of the website can at any time deem content to be objectionable and can remove it from the site. This site does not endorse any user generated content that is posted on the site. Members will not post copyrighted content without permission from the owner. Members understand content — whether it be text, graphic, or audio visual — is the sole responsibility of the person from which such content originated. This site is no way responsible for the accuracy, integrity, or quality of such content.

**Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms and message boards available for every community group featured on the site. Your first and last name will be displayed during chat sessions or when you post something in the message boards. Any additional information you choose to submit in these areas is considered public. To protect yourself from unwanted spam or other unsolicited or unwanted communication, you are advised against providing personally identifiable information, including email addresses, postal addresses, and phone numbers. This site does not monitor the chat rooms unless we receive a request to do so by a member via Customer Support.

**Links to Other Sites**  
This site contains links to other sites. This site is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

**Updates to This Privacy Policy**  
This site has the right to make changes or additions to this policy at any time. If those changes involve using your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time you joined, the site will notify you by email. Changes that do not affect use of personally identifiable information will be posted to the site. If you have questions regarding this policy, please check this policy periodically or contact Customer Support.

**Contacting the Website**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact Customer Support. 

* * *

### Website Security Policy 

#### Website Security Policy for Clients

iModules Software treats the security of its client’s data with utmost importance. We take many precautions at the infrastructure and software layers to deliver the highest level of protection for your constituent data and sensitive information. iModules owns and operates the database and web servers that host clients' websites and store their data. These servers are protected by securely configured firewalls that prevent data from being accessed via the Internet. Each client's data is stored in a dedicated database; this prevents the intrusion or corruption of data. In addition, clients' data catalogs cannot see or access each other's data.

**SSL**  
Login, electronic commerce, and administrative activity is transmitted over an industry standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL).

**Logins and Passwords**  
Strong passwords are required for each login, and they are stored in a salted, hashed format that cannot be read by administrators or employees. Multiple failed logins or lost login requests are challenged by reCaptcha. An administrative rights system restricts authenticated but unauthorized access to constituent data.

**Personally Identifiable Information (PII)**  
The collection, storage, or display of Personally Identifiable Information (PII) in iModules’ Application Services or use of iModules’ Web Services is prohibited. For example, (i) PII items relating to: Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA); (ii) Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA); or (iii) government issued identifications, including, but not limited to, Social Security Numbers, Driver License Numbers, and Individual Taxpayer Identification Numbers. 

To the extent other personal constituent information, or Personal Data (as defined below), is stored in our platform; such information shall be treated as confidential information by iModules. For purposes of iModules’ Application Services or Web Services, Personal Data may include: name, address, other contact information, mother’s maiden name, encrypted date of birth, etc. As previously noted, iModules takes reasonable security measures to protect all information provided by clients, including Personal Data relating to constituents. However, clients acknowledge that they are solely responsible for inputting and managing such Personal Data and comply with all applicable laws governing Personal Data.

All date of birth data values are stored encrypted. Please note we do not allow clients to store any PII relating to Social Security Numbers, Driver License Numbers, or any other government issued identification. 

**PCI Compliance**  
iModules maintains compliance with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) and is certified compliant as a Level One Service Provider by a Qualified Security Assessor (QSA) authorized by the PCI Security Standards Council. iModules' processes, procedures, network configuration, and overall environment conform to all of the security guidelines as defined in the PCI DSS standard and are annually verified by an external auditor. This Level One compliance, the highest level of PCI DSS compliance, helps ensure your e-commerce transaction data is securely protected, transmitted, and stored by iModules. As part of iModules policy, datacenters hosting the Encompass platform must maintain their own annual SSAE 16 audit. Upon request, iModules shall provide the current attestation of compliance for PCI DSS as well as provide a certified SSAE 16, or equivalent review, performed and completed by an external audit firm, on behalf of the datacenter used for iModules Encompass platform.
